<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Men on Peer counseling in Tokyo</title>
    <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/tags/men/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Men on Peer counseling in Tokyo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:21:56 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/tags/men/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Feeling bad about feeling bad can make you feel worse</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2017/08/10feeling-bad-about-feeling-bad-can-make-you-feel-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 12:43:04 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2017/08/10feeling-bad-about-feeling-bad-can-make-you-feel-worse/</guid>
      <description>Pressure to feel upbeat can make you feel downbeat, while embracing your darker moods can actually make you feel better in the long run, according to new UC Berkeley research.
“We found that people who habitually accept their negative emotions experience fewer negative emotions, which adds up to better psychological health,” said study senior author Iris Mauss, an associate professor of psychology at UC Berkeley.
Read more at http://news.berkeley.edu/2017/08/10/emotionalacceptance/</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Our group is growing</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2017/07/18our-group-is-growing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:21:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2017/07/18our-group-is-growing/</guid>
      <description>Seven men in attendance tonight, including two new men.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is peer counseling?</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/about/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Confidential listening; just a place to get things off your chest. Come talk about whatever is important to you, and be heard by men who care.
Tokyo men&amp;rsquo;s circle is part of The Mankind Project (http://mankindproject.org/) which supports men in finding their authentic selves and living their mission in the world.
Some of the men in the Tokyo circle have attended a weekend experiential training called New Warrior Training Adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Location</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/location/</guid>
      <description>Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Group currently meets in Hiroo on 1st and 3rd Tuesdays. We meet in the office of one of our members, so the venue is available for our circle at no cost.
Email tokyoATmypowercircle.org for questions or more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/calendar/</guid>
      <description>Doors open at 6:45pm. Meetings start promptly at 7pm.
Tokyo Men&amp;rsquo;s Circle meets on 1st and 3rd Tuesdays each month.
Tokyo co-gender Circle meets on 2nd and 4th Tuesdays each month.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Agreements</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/agreements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/agreements/</guid>
      <description>Confidentiality. Nothing said by other men in the circle can be spoken about outside of circles. You may not even say which men were at circle. You may, however, talk about your own experience. No drugs or alcohol. If you are high or have been drinking, tell the group. Honor this sacred space. Arrive on time. Punctuality is very important, as it reinforces integrity. We’re not here to fix people.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Men&#39;s Group Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2016/08/09the-mens-group-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 18:21:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2016/08/09the-mens-group-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>(posted by Takeshi on Facebook)
 The men&amp;rsquo;s group is a safe place to discuss anything that is weighing on our hearts out minds. Anything that is said in the group remains in the group.
It&amp;rsquo;s not a social gathering; there&amp;rsquo;s no smoking, drinking, eating.. But we are a close knit group. Over time we get to know each other well, and this requires a commitment to the work.. this is really a commitment to yourself to improve yourself and become the man you are meant to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Revitalizing MKP in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2015/09/25revitalizing-mkp-in-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2015 11:57:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tokyo.mypowercircle.org/post/2015/09/25revitalizing-mkp-in-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>Three remaining members of Tokyo I-group met last night and expressed interest in expanding our community which has been in hibernation for some years.
Our next meeting is scheduled for Friday October 23rd (2015) in Hiroo. This meeting is only for MKP men, but we will be discussing ways to expand the group, and probably include new men at future meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
